[{"answer": " Hello, Rachel.  Its nice to meet you.  My name is Denis", "docId": "01-04", "aSentId": 14, "question": "", "qSentId": 13},{"answer": " Its nice to meet you", "docId": "01-04", "aSentId": 15, "question": " Hello, Rachel.  Its nice to meet you.  My name is Denis", "qSentId": 14},{"answer": " Hows your interview going so far", "docId": "01-04", "aSentId": 16, "question": " Its nice to meet you", "qSentId": 15},{"answer": " I think its going pretty well.  It seems like a very interesting position and th", "docId": "01-04", "aSentId": 17, "question": " Hows your interview going so far", "qSentId": 16},{"answer": " Yes, we have a great work environment here.  Well, our meeting is a chance fo", "docId": "01-04", "aSentId": 21, "question": " I think its going pretty well.  It seems like a very interesting position and th", "qSentId": 20},{"answer": " OK", "docId": "01-04", "aSentId": 26, "question": " Yes, we have a great work environment here.  Well, our meeting is a chance fo", "qSentId": 25},{"answer": " First of all, lets talk about salary.  The salary for the position youre applying fo", "docId": "01-04", "aSentId": 27, "question": " OK", "qSentId": 26},{"answer": " That sounds very fair.  Actually, Ive been a student up until now and I wa", "docId": "01-04", "aSentId": 34, "question": " First of all, lets talk about salary.  The salary for the position youre applying fo", "qSentId": 33},{"answer": " Good.  Its a very competitive salary for the type of position", "docId": "01-04", "aSentId": 38, "question": " That sounds very fair.  Actually, Ive been a student up until now and I wa", "qSentId": 37},{"answer": " I have one question about the salary", "docId": "01-04", "aSentId": 39, "question": " Good.  Its a very competitive salary for the type of position", "qSentId": 38},{"answer": " Sure", "docId": "01-04", "aSentId": 40, "question": " I have one question about the salary", "qSentId": 39},{"answer": " Are employees paid overtime for any extra hours they work", "docId": "01-04", "aSentId": 41, "question": " Sure", "qSentId": 40},{"answer": " No, with a salaried position like this one employees are not paid overtime.  Youl", "docId": "01-04", "aSentId": 42, "question": " Are employees paid overtime for any extra hours they work", "qSentId": 41},{"answer": " All right", "docId": "01-04", "aSentId": 47, "question": " No, with a salaried position like this one employees are not paid overtime.  Youl", "qSentId": 46},{"answer": " The company also offers a very attractive benefits package and retiremen", "docId": "01-04", "aSentId": 48, "question": " All right", "qSentId": 47},{"answer": " Oh, yes.  I was reading about that on the companys website", "docId": "01-04", "aSentId": 52, "question": " The company also offers a very attractive benefits package and retiremen", "qSentId": 51},{"answer": " We offer a very good medical, vision, and dental insurance plan.  Also, th", "docId": "01-04", "aSentId": 53, "question": " Oh, yes.  I was reading about that on the companys website", "qSentId": 52},{"answer": " That does sound very good", "docId": "01-04", "aSentId": 57, "question": " We offer a very good medical, vision, and dental insurance plan.  Also, th", "qSentId": 56},{"answer": " Ill give you this information packet on the company benefits.  It explains all o", "docId": "01-04", "aSentId": 58, "question": " That does sound very good", "qSentId": 57},{"answer": " Sure, Ill do that", "docId": "01-04", "aSentId": 63, "question": " Ill give you this information packet on the company benefits.  It explains all o", "qSentId": 62},{"answer": " The company also offers some other great perks: every employee gets ", "docId": "01-04", "aSentId": 64, "question": " Sure, Ill do that", "qSentId": 63},{"answer": " That sounds great.  Ive never had a company car though.  How does tha", "docId": "01-04", "aSentId": 69, "question": " The company also offers some other great perks: every employee gets ", "qSentId": 68},{"answer": " The company owns the car, but you drive it and get to keep it as if it were you", "docId": "01-04", "aSentId": 71, "question": " That sounds great.  Ive never had a company car though.  How does tha", "qSentId": 70},{"answer": " Wow!  Thats a great perk", "docId": "01-04", "aSentId": 77, "question": " The company owns the car, but you drive it and get to keep it as if it were you", "qSentId": 76},{"answer": "All the details of the company car are in the information packet I just gave yo", "docId": "01-04", "aSentId": 81, "question": " Wow!  Thats a great perk", "qSentId": 80},{"answer": " OK, thank you", "docId": "01-04", "aSentId": 85, "question": "All the details of the company car are in the information packet I just gave yo", "qSentId": 84},{"answer": " So, do you have any other questions youd lilke to ask me about the pay an", "docId": "01-04", "aSentId": 86, "question": " OK, thank you", "qSentId": 85},{"answer": " I dont think so.  I think you answered all the questions I had", "docId": "01-04", "aSentId": 90, "question": " So, do you have any other questions youd lilke to ask me about the pay an", "qSentId": 89},{"answer": " OK.  Well, take a look through that information packet.  My contact information i", "docId": "01-04", "aSentId": 91, "question": " I dont think so.  I think you answered all the questions I had", "qSentId": 90},{"answer": " I will.  Thank you", "docId": "01-04", "aSentId": 95, "question": " OK.  Well, take a look through that information packet.  My contact information i", "qSentId": 94},{"answer": " Its been nice talking to you, and I look forward to potentially working with you i", "docId": "01-04", "aSentId": 96, "question": " I will.  Thank you", "qSentId": 95},{"answer": " Thank you.  I hope to see you soon", "docId": "01-04", "aSentId": 100, "question": " Its been nice talking to you, and I look forward to potentially working with you i", "qSentId": 99},{"answer": " Bye-bye", "docId": "01-04", "aSentId": 101, "question": " Thank you.  I hope to see you soon", "qSentId": 100}]
